jpegmini.com 2014-02-17

# JPEGmini | Privacy Policy

Updated: June 20, 2013

Jpegmini.com (" **Site** "), operated by ICVT Ltd. (" **ICVT** "), provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection and use of personal information we receive from users who visit the Site and use any or our services offered thereon (" **Service** ").

Your privacy is very important to us and we employ reasonable measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access.

#### Information Collection

In the course of using the Service you may provide us with personally identifiable information. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you, and information on your use of and activities at our Site that may be connected with you ("Personal Information"). Personal Information collected may include your name, email address, phone number, gender, birthday, account credentials for Facebook, Google, Flickr and Picasa and information regarding your use of our Service. Personal Information may also include information you supply concerning your preferences and interests expressed in the course of use of our Service.

When you visit the Site and register to our service, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a Site. This information may include, but is not limited to, technical information about your computer such as memory, bandwidth etc., Internet Protocol address, browser type, the web page you were visiting before you came to our Site and information you search for on our Service. Such information is collected by us for technical reasons and in order to improve our Service. We may also collect statistical and other data related to your use of the Service, usage patterns and/or other behavioral information. This information is collected and used as non-individually identifiable information.

Our Software [may collect information regarding the use of the Software, such as the number, resolution and file size of optimized photos in each session and overall, statistics of pressing different buttons in the app, errors and failures. This information is sent to third party service providers which analyze and integrate this information. We use this information to improve our Software and our Services. We do not collect any personally identifiable information or meta-data which can be used to identify the location in which photos were taken or the person who took the photos or the persons appearing in the photos. We do not make any copies of the photos and do not have access to the photos. Currently the collection of information only applies in our JPEGmini for Mac Software. You may opt-out of collecting such information in the preferences menu of our JPEGmini for Mac Software.

When you purchase the Software through our Site you will be redirected to one of our third party partners, either B&H, Kagi or the Apple App Store ("Vendor Partners"). In order to purchase the Software in our Vendor Partners' websites you will need to provide them with details such as your credit card number, CVV number, its expiration date and any other details needed in order to facilitate the transaction. The websites of our Vendor Partners have different privacy policies and we urge you to review these as well. We are not responsible for any information provided to our Vendor Partners and we do not receive any payment details (such as credit card numbers) from them.

#### Use of Information

We use your Personal Information for providing our Service and for providing communications related to our Site and Service, including for (i) process and reply of your requests, (ii) provide marketing materials (iii) support related issues, notices about updates, new features, or other information of interest to our users regarding the above.

ICVT does not share, distribute, sell or rent any of your Personal Information with/to third parties, except in the following circumstances: 

  1. If the information is required by law in order to prevent, investigate, or take action regarding illegal activities, situations involving potential threats to physical safety, rights, property or of any person, suspected fraud and violations of our Terms of Use. In addition, We will share information in respond to legal process, court orders, subpoenas, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  2. For the purpose of providing and operating ICVT's Site or ICVT's Service, we may share information with trusted third-party partners who need to know for purpose of providing the Service to you. We will require that these third parties comply with this Privacy Policy.
  3. If ICVT becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will notify you before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy, through your email address or by placing a prominent notice on our Site. 
  4. If we have your permission to do so.

Any data processing performed by these third parties will, if and when required by law, be governed by data processing agreement in the form required by law, preserving your statutory data protection rights.

This Privacy Policy is not applicable to other websites. If you employ our Service with or through other technologies and/or services offered by any other websites, we encourage you to review such third party websites terms of use and privacy policy.

#### Cookies

Like many Sites, we use cookies or similar technology to collect information. [A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use persistent cookies to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Site; and we use session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Site, to better understand how you interact with the Site and to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on the Site. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the Sites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of our services.

We use information we obtain by technical means (such as the automatic recording performed by our servers or through the use of cookies or through the data obtained by a 3rd party service) for the above purposes and in order to monitor and analyze use of the Site and our services and for the Site's technical administration, to increase our Site and service's functionality and user-friendliness, to better tailor it to your needs, to generate and derive useful data and information concerning the interests, characteristics and usage behavior of our users, and to verify that visitors to the Site meet the criteria required to process their requests.

#### E-mail Communications

At any time, you have the ability to opt out of receiving marketing communications from ICVT, but you may not opt out of administrative emails (for example, emails about your transactions or policy changes) while you are a registered user. You can opt out by either changing your e-mail preferences or using the link provided at the bottom of each email message.

We do not send emails to anyone without permission, and we do not sell or rent email addresses to any unauthorized third party. This does not mean that we can prevent spam from happening on the Internet. If you believe that you have received an unsolicited email from us, please contact us at the e-mail below and we will investigate. 

#### Changing or Deleting Your Information

All registered users may review, update or correct the Personal Information provided in their registration or account profile by changing their user preferences in their account. If you choose to opt out entirely, then your account may become deactivated and you will need to re-register should you decide to opt-in again. To delete your account entirely, please email us at [support@jpegmini.com](mailto:support@jpegmini.com). You should protect your password from disclosure because anyone who gains access to your password may have access (and may make edits) to your profile and Personal Information.

#### Policy Towards Children

This Site is not directed to children under 18. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [support@jpegmini.com](mailto:support@jpegmini.com). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

#### International Transfers

Our Service may be provided using resources and servers located in various countries around the world. Therefore your personal data may be transferred across international borders outside the country where you use our Service, including countries that do not have laws providing specific protection for personal data or that have different legal rules on data protection. In such cases we take steps to ensure that there is a legal basis for such a transfer and that adequate protection for your personal data is provided as required by applicable law, for example, by using standard agreements approved by relevant authorities (where necessary) and by requiring the use of other appropriate technical and organizational information security measures.

#### Security

We have implemented suitable security policies, rules and technical measures in order to protect and safeguard the Personal Information that we collect. We limit access to your Personal Information only to employees who need to have access to such information in order to provide you all the activities related to the Service. However, you should be aware that there is no data that is transmitted over the Internet that can be guaranteed 100% secure in transmission or safe from theft or illegal capture.

#### Links

The Service may contain links to third parties' web sites. While we attempt to provide links to sites that value your privacy, we cannot be responsible for the content or privacy policies of such sites. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of such third parties' Web sites linked or provided through the Service prior to any use of such Web sites.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy 

We reserve the right to change the provisions of the Privacy Policy from time to time and you are therefore advised to check it regularly. If we make any significant changes in the way we treat personal information, we will notify through your email address or by placing a prominent notice on our site. **Your continued use of the Site and/or Service after any change to this policy constitutes your acceptance of the terms of the amended Privacy Policy.**

#### Contact

For any privacy concern regarding this Site or Service please email us at: [support@jpegmini.com](mailto:support@jpegmini.com)  
Alternatively, we can be reached at our postal mail address:   
ICVT Ltd., 23 Menachem Begin Rd., Tel Aviv, Israel
